hotdealsclub.com 2011-12-31

# Hot Deals Club - Privacy Policy

**HOT DEALS CLUB - PRIVACY POLICY AND ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY**  
HotDealsClub.com, TheHotDeals.com, TheDeals.Net, Hot-Deals.org, Hot-Deals.net 

Hot Deals Club is a registered trademark of Website Network LLC, whose mission is to find the best deals on the Internet and encourage fair information exchange practices. 

We certainly don't like legal mumbo jumbo, but it is necessary to list the acceptable use of the Hot Deals Club to help keep this site alive. The acceptable use policy (AUP) of the Hot Deals Club: 

  * The Hot Deals Club ("we" or "us" or "our") encourages fair information exchange on the topic of good deals. We wrote software, websites, and RSS Feeds that help deliver content to visitors of our websites. We support the free flow of information and ideas over the Internet. All data posted on the Hot Deals Club is for the sole use of visitors to the Hot Deals Club websites and RSS Datafeeds. Our data cannot be re-sold or plagiarized without written permission from Website Network LLC, the owner of the Hot Deals Club. 
  * The Hot Deals Club website and content can only be viewed by entering a website address ("URL") that is owned by Website Network LLC, with the exception website publishers who have been licensed to copy our content for their use. People can integrate Hot Deals Club RSS Datafeeds into their websites, but must say the data came from the Hot Deals Club, and not to falsely claim the data as their own. _No Hot Deals Club information/data/website may be altered or changed in any way_ without expressed written permission from Website Network LLC. Any website or publisher that copies Hot Deals Club text or data and makes the Hot Deals Club information appear as their own, will be in copyright infringement. 
  * Any website not licensed by Website Network LLC that makes their content appear to be from the Hot Deals Club, makes their URL appear to be the Hot Deals Club, or makes people believe they manage the Hot Deals Club is not allowed. This includes, but not limited to, any website address ("URL") with the words "hot", "deals" and "club", or any website that masks itself as Hot Deals Club when it is not. 
  * The Hot Deals Club does not control our users' opinions inferred after reading the information displayed on the Hot Deals Club. The Hot Deals Club is strictly an information tool, and our users must make their own intelligent decisions on what to infer by reading the information posted on the Hot Deals Club. 
  * The Hot Deals Club makes every effort possible to ensure the information written on the site is accurate and legitimate, however does not guarantee that any information is accurate or legitimate. 
  * Users may only submit deals and information to us that are considered _public information_ (information that can be publically obtained). Anyone who submits private company secrets without permission from that company, may be breaking the law and may be liable for damages caused by leaking private information. Therefore, submitters must comply with local, state, federal, or non United States law or regulation regarding exchange of information. 
  * Someone who submits an email addrss to the Hot Deals Club must be the one person who reads all email sent to that address. Email addresses may be stored in our database for the purpose of sending information on hot deals to that email address. If a user sends us an email address requesting we send them email back, that user must be the owner and operator of that email address. The Hot Deals Club does not send unsolicited email, and will honor requests to remove an email address from our database if the owner of that address does not want to receive emails from us. 
  * Maliciously effecting the security or bandwidth of the Hot Deals Club is prohibited, and we do make an effort to squash potential violators. Security breaches include, but are not limited to, accessing data of which the user is not an intended recipient, port scans, flood pings, packet spoofing, forging ip addresses, and forging email addresses. 
  * The Hot Deals Club is like a portal, that directs users to other websites. The Hot Deals Club is not a merchant site, does not sell any products, and cannot support anyone who makes purchases on other websites. When a user leaves the Hot Deals Club website (a Hot Deals Club URL no longer appears in the browser's URL address box), the Hot Deals Club no longer supports or guarantees the user's session. The Hot Deals Club makes tremendous effort to ensure all sites listed are legitimate, but cannot actually guarantee that each sites are legitimate. Users must use their own discretion and their own personal liability in their own security when entering personal information or credit card information on websites, and the Hot Deals Club cannot guarantee that users' information will be secure when submitting to those websites. Users are responsible for any orders placed on merchant's websites, and the Hot Deals Club cannot guarantee that orders will be fulfilled as promised by those sites. The Hot Deals Club and Website Network LLC are not liable for information stolen or orders not fulfilled when a user is directed to a merchant's website, since the merchant is ultimately responsible for maintaining security on their site. 
  * No one may bid on the words "Hot Deals Club" on any advertising engine. 
  * Stealing the identity of the Hot Deals Club or Website Network is against the law. 
  * Knowingly altering the data, text, information, or code presented by the Hot Deals Club is in violation of copyright laws. 
  * The Hot Deals Club may ban or take legal action against any person or entity who violates the Acceptible Use Policy or Privacy Policy of the Hot Deals Club. This is necessary to help protect the longevity of the site, the qualify of our information, and the security of our users. 
  * The acceptable use policy may change at any time without notice. 

* * *

Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and will notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site 
  2. The organization collecting the information 
  3. How the information is used 
  4. With whom the information may be shared 
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Hot Deals Club control 
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact THe Hot Deals Maniac by sending us email. Our email address can be found at the very top of the Hot Deals Club website front page. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
  
Hot Deals Club is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Hot Deals Club collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
  
This web site contains mostly links to other sites. Please be aware that we (Hot Deals Club) are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Registration**  
  
Some areas of this website may require the user to first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**Cookies**  
  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Cookies can enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. The Hot Deals Club uses cookies to track some users that visit the site, for the purpose of collecting trend information on users which ultimately will allow us to deliver better content. The Hot Deals Club may collect information on how many times each person clicks on a deal, how many times a user visits the site, and from what region the user comes from. Advertisements on the site may use cookies to track users. When a user clicks on a link on the Hot Deals Club, the target site may collect information regarding the user's session and may know that the user came from the Hot Deals Club. 

**Log Files**  
  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
  
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**Mailing List**  
  
Only invited users may subscribe to our mailing list. If an invited user wishes to subscribe to our mailing list, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

**Surveys & Contests**  
  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Security**  
  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

**Supplementation of Information**  
  
In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our visitors, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. In order for this website to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the browsing & clicking habits of users with similar information from our partners, Hot Deals Club, and Website Network, to create a personalized user profile. When a user clicks on a link within the Hot Deals Club domain, we log the clickthroughs so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences. We will not disclose specific information (such as IP address, time & date) about our users' clicks. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service(s), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done by emailing the Hot Deals Maniac. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
  
Our users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our mailing list has an "opt-out" mechanism so members can cancel their subscriptions at any time.   
  
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

**Notification of Changes**  
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Emails**  
  
If you wish to submit a "hot deal" or talk to the author of this website, you may send email to the Hot Deals Maniac. From time to time, we may decide to share your email with the other visitors on this site. Thus, emails received by the Hot Deals Club are subject to being posting on this website, unless the sender requests that their email not be posted. If we decide to post your email letter on this website, it will be stripped of any information that can personally identify the sender, such as full name, email address, location, personal website addresses, and phone number, unless the email we received was threatening or abusive. Please note that due to a heavy amount of emails we receive, the person who responds to your email may be a privlidged member of the Hot Deals Club, not necessarilly the owner of the Hot Deals Club or the "Hot Deals Maniac".
